http://www.nineronline.com/site/privacy.html

Charlotte, NC
(28223)
Today
Generally sunny despite a few afternoon clouds. High around 65F. Winds light and variable..
Tonight
Partly cloudy skies during the evening will give way to cloudy skies overnight. Low around 45F. Winds light and variable.
Español
Privacy PolicyProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.ninertimes.com and Student Niner Media Department of the University of North Carolina at Charlotte and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Student Niner Media Department of the University of North Carolina at Charlotte include www.ninertimes.com, Student Niner Media, www.sanskritmagazine.com and www.radiofreecharlotte.com. The Student Niner Media website is a news, information, and entertainment site. By using the Student Niner Media website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationPlease keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Student Niner Media’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our site; (b) entering and sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or product you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.Sharing Information with Third PartiesStudent Niner Media does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.Student Niner Media may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Student Niner Media, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Student Niner Media may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Student Niner Media or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Student Niner Media; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Student Niner Media, or the public.Automatically Collected InformationInformation about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Student Niner Media. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Student Niner Media website.Use of CookiesThe Student Niner Media website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Student Niner Media pages, or register with Student Niner Media site or services, a cookie helps Student Niner Media to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Student Niner Media website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Student Niner Media features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Student Niner Media services or websites you visit.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Security of your Personal InformationStudent Niner Media secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Student Niner Media uses the following methods for this purpose:-          SSL ProtocolWhen personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.Children Under ThirteenStudent Niner Media does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age or thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.Opting-OutAs described above, we and third parties may use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate serving relevant ads to you. For example, these technologies help us tailor ads and content to you if you have visited our site before. In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies as described above, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising by visiting http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2FChanges to this StatementStudent Niner Media reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about any significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgement of the modified Privacy Policy: and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.Contact InformationStudent Niner Media welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Student Niner Media has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Student Niner Media at:Student Niner MediaUniversity of North Carolina at Charlotte9201 University City Blvd.PMSU 042ACharlotte, NC 28223Email Address:studentmedia@uncc.eduTelephone number:704-687-7129Effective as of July 24, 2019
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Instagram
© Copyright 2019 Niner Times, 9201 University City Blvd. SU 042 Charlotte, NC | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
